You must have seen the previous blog that I had
left Ranchi and this blog that you will see now, I was
not able to find this clip
and the blog that you will see now, this blog was
deleted, then I took it out from recent delete and
edited it again, I thought
that the block was lifted but this was blocked, so
finally you guys enjoy this blog, so this
is gas, welcome to your new blog, right now it is
afternoon time and now I am going and
starting the blog, today is finally
after a long time, fish is being made in Ranchi, your
brother's favourite and look here, what is Suman
doing, right now we are giving it a good grind, I
mean
both of us will grind it, it is done, there is no
masala left, right now
Mashaallah, I mean for grinding, I have taken out all the
spices, salted ginger, everything is fine,
I will rub it twice, it is not yours
only, otherwise I would have done it brother, I will do it
[Music]
ok
[Music] let us
know a little bit about
that masala and here on the side
gas, finally I got to eat it brother,
after a lot of fear brother, I wanted to tell you once that
brother, yesterday the name of the thief had
gone, so much kilograms were found.
Which Suman
[Sangeet] is going to do, please
tell us in the comments, we are getting the
gas filled right now,
give us 100 rupees
and then we will see, we will give you a surprise on YouTube.